kellycodetectors.com 2012-11-16

# Privacy Policy - Kellyco Metal Detector Superstore

### Privacy Policy:

**What information do we collect?**

  * We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
  * When making a purchase we will ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
  * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**How do we protect visitor information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

**Do we use "cookies"?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.

**Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

**Changes to our policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on May 16, 2008.

**Questions and feedback**  
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.

**Your consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Kellyco Metal Detector SuperStore 1085 Belle Ave. Winter Springs, Florida 32708 - Toll FREE: 1-888-KELLYCO (1-888-535-5926)  \- Questions or Comments - Please e-mail us [here](mailto:customerservice@kellycodetectors.com).   
All words and photographs are © 1998 - 2012 Kellyco Metal Detector Distributors unless otherwise noted. All rights reserved. Any use or retransmission of text or images on this website without written consent of the copyright owner constitutes copyright infringement and is prohibited. **Enjoy your metal detector and happy hunting! Published SAVE, SAVE UP TO and SAVING Percentages are based on Manufactures MSRP (Manufacturers Suggested Retail Price) list price or (compared to price) or/and total combined savings of metal detector and its bundled accessories. Not responsible for typographical errors, mistakes or manufacturers inability to ship a product.**
